how many of you
believe that evolution is a
counterfeit I believe that evolution is
a counterfeit and and in fact if you are
a 7-Day Adventist you you should
definitely believe that evolution is a
counterfeit amen so um I'm a little bit
nervous but I'm going to ask you just to
say nice and Loud if you can if you can
with me you believe evolution is clearly
a
counterfeit amen amen I believe that God
created the world uh in six days and he
rested on the seventh so let's talk a
little bit about Evolution there's some
just a couple of components I want you
to to to focus on this morning number
one uh um evolution is the concept that
out of chaos came order over long
periods of time yeah that's what the
evolutionist believe that that that
order uh came out of chaos and that it
took long periods of time but eventually
it happened order came out of chaos
that's number one number two uh
evolutionists believe that humans
evolved from lower forms of life um or
that uh humans and apes have have uh a
common ancestor okay so somehow Or
Another We're related to animals and and
in fact we evolved from lower forms of
life simply meaning that over time we
got better okay over time things get
better things are evolving and going
higher and higher so number one our
order came out of chaos and number two
that things evolved that that man
evolved uh uh from uh uh lower forms of
life to higher forms of life we advance
we grow we get
better over time number three is the
principle of adaptation and basically
this teaches that certain species uh
survive based on their ability to
what to adapt to their environment and
so if you've heard the term
survival of the what of the fittest
right that is what that is talking about
the ability to adapt to your environment
and thus survive so three things that we
need to remember number one
evolutionists believe that chaos that
order came out of Chaos number two
evolutionists believe that humans
evolved from lower forms of life to
higher forms of life that that we uh um
we got better over time let's put it
that way number three uh adaptation that
that we survive based on our ability to
adapt to our particular environment and
so evolution is really all about the
process of change and how that change
occurred
so the faith of an evolutionist is to be
admired what do you think the faith of
an evolutionist is to be admired why
because uh the faith of of an
evolutionist leads him to believe things
that he has not
seen now do we need that kind of Faith
yeah absolutely the faith of an
evolutionist is to be admired uh um he
he has no evidence in the past he has no
evidence in the present and he has no
access to the Future and yet he
believes that's pretty strong faith what
do you think yeah and we would do well
to learn a lesson from
evolutionists because they have very
very very strong faith how many of you
would like to have strong faith too yeah
and remember strong faith is very
important because Jesus said listen if
you don't have strong faith Satan is
going to do what he's going to sift you
okay so listen carefully the
evolutionist has faith that order came
out of chaos yes yeah the evolutionist
has faith that man evolved over time
from worse to better uh that he evolved
from lower forms of life to higher forms
of life and number three the
evolutionist believes that man survives
today that the species that are are here
today survive because of their ability
to adapt to the
environment an evolutionist has faith
that must be admired must be admired so
here's a question and yes it is a trick
question evolution is a counterfeit yes
what is it a counterfeit of
it's a counterfeit of what creation it's
a counterfeit of creation yeah okay let
me share with you the definition of a
counterfeit to
counterfeit means to illegally it
imitate something counterfeit products
are often produced with the intent to
take advantage of the superior value of
the imitated product so a counterfeit is
something that looks like
the genuine amen okay has anyone ever
seen a counterfeit $7 bill you ever seen
one of
those okay now if a $7 Bill were were
were you happen to see a $7 Bill uh you
could not say it was a counterfeit
because there's no what genuine $7 Bill
amen but there is a genuine $1 bill and
a $10 bill so are there counterfeit $10
bills bills yes which means the
counterfeit $10 bill looks just like the
genuine $10
bill I want to suggest to you this this
morning that evolution is not a
counterfeit of
creation evolution is it is a
counterfeit but it is not a counterfeit
of creation
let me share with you why want you to
turn with me to the Book of Genesis I'm
sorry Psalm 33 Psalm
33 now please don't get me wrong I I am
not saying that that that Satan is not
using Evolution teaching it in the place
of creation that's not what I'm saying
I'm just saying that Evolution uh as
counterfeit as it is is not a
counterfeit of creation because the two
look very
different are you with me so listen
listen listen to what happens go with me
to Psalm 33 Psalm 33 and verse 6 Psalm
33 I want you to notice with
me verse
6 all right Psalm 33:6 by the word of
the Lord were the heavens made and all
the host of him by the breath of his
mouth verse n for he spake and it was
what done he commanded and
what it stood
fast he commanded and it stood fast so
in essence what the Bible's telling us
is that when God created the Earth he
spoke and what happened it was done it
was there he spoke it was done it was
immediate
amen what is evolution
teach that that that that the our Earth
came into existence by the process of in
other words long time periods passed for
our Earth to get to the condition that
it was now is evolution a
counterfeit yes is it error yes but it
is not a counterfeit of creation because
Evolution looks nothing like
creation God SP broke and it was done
the picture of creation if we were to
put a picture of creation and then a
picture of evolution the two would look
very different are you with me so far so
what we're going to find out today is
that Evolution yes it is a counterfit
but of
what that's the question of what so
listen let's go to the Book of Genesis
chapter
3 Genesis chapter
3 and let's notice some things
here about what happened at the very
beginning of time Genesis chapter 3
beginning with verse three uh but the
fruit of the of the tree this is Satan
or Eve speaking to The Serpent and the
serpent is responding to her but listen
to what Eve says but of the fruit of the
tree which is in the midst of the garden
God has said ye shall not eat of it
neither shall you touch it lest you die
and the serpent said unto the woman
what you shall not surely die Okay so
what is Satan doing
here he's lying and what is he lying
about he's lying about
God's God's word yeah he says and what
what is his lie about God's
word you will not die so check it out
God says listen in the day that you eat
you will die Satan says oh God's word is
not going to come to what die no no no
no no his word is not going to be
fulfilled his word is not going to be
fulfilled and as a result Eve believes
this lie that God's word does not get
fulfilled in other words we can we can
say it like this she
loses faith
in the word of
God that God's word will do what it
says it's going to do so as a result of
believing this lie and as a result of
doubting the the sure word of God Eve
reaches for the tree she eats and as a
result sin enters into the
world
why because in a sense we might say that
their
faith
failed
failed okay in other words look my trust
in the word of God that it's going to do
what it says it's going to do y yeah I
don't think his word is going to come to
pass I don't think that that I'm really
going to die I don't think that God's
word really means what it says and
therefore they lost faith or trust in
the word of God and as a result
sin enters so let me ask you a question
if that is the case then what is the
purpose of the Plan of
Salvation what is the purpose of the
Plan of Salvation for mankind if they
lost faith in God's word then what is
God trying to
restore faith in his word are you with
me so far amen okay that please follow
this very carefully so the purpose of
God is to restore faith in man to
restore faith in the word of God so
notice with me the book of Romans
chapter 1
Romans chapter
1 Romans chapter 1 verse
16 is it up on oh is it up on the screen
there we go Romans
1 verse
16 the Bible says here
for I am not ashamed of the gospel of
Christ for it is a power of God unto
salvation to everyone that believeth to
the Jew first and also to the Greek for
therein is the righteousness of God
revealed from what faith to Faith as it
is written the just shall live by faith
so the purpose of the Gospel is to bring
us into a faith relationship with God
Amen all right so the just shall live by
what faith so check it out in
Creation in
creation God speaks and as soon as he
speaks what
happens it comes to pass right but then
Adam and Eve or um Eve loses Faith or
trust in the word of
God and believe Satan's lie
so now what must God teach
Humanity he must teach
them he must teach them Faith he must
teach them faith I want you to
notice Romans chapter 8 with me Romans
chapter 8 verse
24 you see I want to suggest to you that
after sin entered there was an
adaptation in the word of God what I
just say
there was an adaptation does that word
sound familiar to you there was an
adaptation in the word of God now you're
saying wait a minute Pastor the word of
God never changes and that's not what
I'm saying there was an adaptation not
in the nature of the word of God but in
the function of the word of
God what do you mean Pastor well listen
look look what Romans chapter 8: 24 says
for we are saved by Hope by what hope
but hope that is
seen is not hope for what a man seeth
why does he yet hope for yeah look at
the next verse let's get the next verse
up there but if we hope for that which
we have not seen then we do with what
patience wait for it now give me another
describe for me
patience okay perseverance would you say
that patience has to do with uh I don't
know like long periods of
time would you say that I would say that
patience means that you have to
know how to how to endure
for long periods of time so look at what
he's saying here look what Paul says he
says look uh uh uh
hope if you can see the hope why are you
hoping you're no longer what hoping but
if you cannot see it then hope continues
on right we don't hope for what we
see otherwise it's no longer
hope right so
Faith Works the same way faith means
that we're waiting for something to
happen and if that something happens
then there's no need
for for Faith so let me ask you a
question let's say that we were back in
creation days before the world is
created and uh and so God begins to
speak Isaiah 55 tells us God's word will
prosper in the thing where to he sent it
amen so so when God spoke in creation
time God says let there be light what
happened so let's say that we were there
in in the creation and we're watching
God create and God says let there be
light would there be any need to
exercise
Faith why
not because as soon as he spake you
would not have time to
Hope amen you wouldn't have time to
exercise Faith well I hope it comes no
no no no because as soon as he speaks
what happens it's
done it's done so so there was no need
to exercise faith when God spoke
something and and said listen this is so
then it was so it was
so however
after Adam and Eve Sinn it appears that
the word of
God went through an
adaptation because
now God
speaks but
what
time how many of you wish that the
creative word of God was here today when
I say the creative word of God I mean
God says God says something all right
um let's see uh you will get that house
and suddenly right there there is the
house Lord I prayed for the house it it
wasn't even a minute and you answered
how many of you would just love oh man I
just wish yeah right but it doesn't work
like that does it God speaks something
and we have to
wait sometimes for long period periods
of
time we have to
exercise patience why let me share with
you why notice with me the book of
Hebrews Hebrews chapter
11 Hebrews chap 11 verse
one Hebrews the 11th
chapter verse one notice what the Bible
says here Hebrews 11:1 now Faith is the
substance of things hoped for the
evidence of Things Not Seen so what is
Faith everyone the substance of things
hoped for the evidence of Things Not
Seen meaning faith is present when you
when you desire something that you do
not yet
have yes that you do not yet possess
otherwise if you possess it faith is no
longer
required yeah so so now the question
then is how does faith
come oh faith comes by hearing and
hearing by the word of God now notice
that doesn't say faith comes by
seeing if I
see then I'll have
faith no no no it's the other way around
faith comes
by hearing and hearing by the word of
God so what does that mean what it means
is very simple that that when God speaks
he is now training our
faith he he did not need to do that
before the fall but now after the fall
okay man needs Faith so here's what I'm
going to do I'm going to
speak and I'm going to allow long
periods of
time to occur
before I
bring
order out
of
chaos oh wait a
minute so you mean you Pastor you
telling me that God is the one that
brings order out of chaos over long
periods
of
time oh wait are you telling me that
evolution is really a counterfeit of
Faith wait a
minute I want you to think about this
remember the points we talked about
remember we we
saw that uh the
evolutionist right uh has faith that
order comes out of chaos over what long
periods of of time well listen let's
take the story of Abraham you guys
remember Abraham right God calls Abraham
out of a very chaotic
situation everyone around him is
involved in idolatry and God says
Abraham and God speaks God what speaks
God says Abraham I'm going to make you
the father of a great
nation you can imagine when Abraham
hears that praise the Lord tells his
wife honey I think tomorrow you're going
to be
pregnant because God just told God told
me that this thing is going to come to
pass and I have faith in the word of God
tomorrow I'm sure than the next couple
of weeks done
deal but is that how it
unfolds no by the end of Abraham life he
has this this chosen child Isaac and
Isaac has two children Jacob and Esau
where is the Great multitude that you
promised me God by the way what does
Abraham
do because
Abraham lost
faith in the word of God what does he
do he takes matters into his own hands
to help the word of God come to
pass in other words Abraham's Faith
failed and he got himself into a very
chaotic
situation anybody ever get themselves
into a very chaotic
situation what I'm telling you today is
fear not because God is the one who
brings
order yeah
he is the one and you might say but lord
it's taken a long time God is saying
don't worry about it I'm trying to
strengthen your
faith so beloved that that theory of
evolution which says which says that
order came out of chaos over long
periods of time if we're looking for the
actual counterfeit or what it's a
counterfeit of we would have to say man
that sounds like
faith that sounds like God speaking his
word and having us go through long
periods of time where he's going to
demonstrate to us that it doesn't matter
how much you mess things up in your life
if you will only have faith in my word I
will bring
order out of
chaos so Abraham ends up in a chaotic
situation and in fact Abraham dies not
having received the
promise Here Comes Jacob and Esau
the word of God is spoken to Jacob in in
reference to Jacob Jacob you your older
brother is going to serve you don't
worry about it you are going to get the
birthright because I've made a promise
to
Abraham the the the seed is going to
come through you so so so Jacob don't
worry but Jacob uh Jacob was probably
thinking all right man the birthright
should be mine when I turn 13
or 18 the age of manhood or whatever it
is but guess what does he get the birth
right when he expects it no and so Jacob
too loses faith in the word of God and
takes matters into his own hands and
brings about an even more chaotic
situation you're probably thinking how
in the world can God now Salvage this
chaotic
situation then we get to
Joseph God speaks the word to Joseph
Joseph your brothers are going to bow
down before you and if we look at the
situation that Joseph goes through he
gets thrown in prison he gets all all
these things happen to
him chaotic things yes but guess what by
the end of the story listen
carefully when the Book of Genesis ends
there is a great multitude of the
children of
Israel now you might say well well well
you know why didn't God just do that in
the very beginning why because God is
trying to strengthen the faith of his
children so he says I'm going to speak a
word and Faith does not come by seeing
it comes by hearing so because I need
your faith to be strengthened I'm going
to speak and then I'm going to allow
long periods of time so that your fath
faith can
be
strengthened I got a question for you
how many of you find yourselves in a
pretty chaotic situation right now don't
raise your hand already too late you're
like me me me me me I know no that's
fine we don't know what the chaotic
situation is but you're in a chaotic
situation and you're wondering God why
don't you come through I've been praying
for eight days now
and we might wonder why God leaves us in
a situation in a predicament but what
I'm trying to tell you beloved is that
God is trying to reveal to you uh his
evolutionary
power is that okay now I know some of
you just got nervous are you saying that
God is in Devil no beloved God created
the world in six days and rested on the
seventh amen so God has cre creative
power amen yes but God also exercises
evolutionary power it is the true
Evolution you're going to see what I
mean as we go along guys so fear not
don't worry about
it evolution in the world is a
counterfeit of genuine
Evolution and what I'm trying to tell
you beloved this morning this afternoon
is that there is a genuine evolution
genuine by the way I love how the Bible
says that God is not the author of
confusion so God is not into chaos God
doesn't bring chaos uh out of order God
brings order out of
chaos so God says listen if you exercise
faith in my word you will understand
what it means to have your faith
strength strengthened and in fact the
Bible tells us that we are to have the
faith of
Jesus yeah so so what is the faith of
Jesus and what does that mean well
listen I got a question for you when
when Jesus performed
miracles did
[Music]
he when Jesus
spoke did he need to wait days and hours
before God
answered no he spoke and it was what it
was done he he he he would you know be
healed man was healed get up man got up
it almost seems like Jesus was was as it
were like excluded from this need of
Faith he wasn't he wasn't but it just
seems like when Jesus spoke everything
was done
yeah but was there a time where Jesus
spoke or asked and it was not done not
done immediately when was that it was in
The Garden of
Gethsemane so now in the garden of
Gethsemane Jesus is praying and perhaps
for the first time we don't know I'm
making the the assumption but perhaps
for the first time I believe for the
first time Jesus prays to his father and
the answer does not come
immediately three times he prays and
it's a new position for Christ because
he's used to his father just he speaks
and as he's speaking it's
done so now what must Jesus depend upon
Faith that's all he has Faith so as he's
being beaten and as he's being spat upon
all he has to depend upon is faith that
God's word will do what it says it will
do so I got a question for you I mean
how many of you ever thought yeah but
you know God said that Jesus would raise
again on the third day right so it
shouldn't have been a challenge yeah
he's going to raise on the third day so
no big deal right hey I'll die and I'll
raise again on the third day yeah but
beloved listen when Jesus begins to
speak to his father even on the cross my
God my God why hast thou what forsaken
me and listen for the first time Jesus
is now left with this with the feeling
that his father is not with
him all he has to depend upon now is
what
faith faith that God's word will bring
him back from from the
grave Jesus enters into death clinging
to the only thing he has his
faith in his father's word so when the
Bible tells us that we have to have the
faith of Jesus what it is saying is that
we have to have a faith that can endure
despite the things that we may see with
our
eyes we must learn how to depend so much
upon the word of of God that when that
when the word of God says something we
say hey it may not come to pass now it
may not even come to pass in my lifetime
but I know because the word of God is
sure and certain that it will come to
pass so you say Pastor how how is this
how is this Evolution a a a counterfeit
of the genuine process of evolution well
let me share with you evolutionist also
have the faith that humans evolved from
lower forms of
life from animal to
man from
Beast to
man that humans
evolved got better as time went
on that humans had a nature that was
like animals at one time
and then as time went on they evolved
and became more like in the image of
man
wow I don't know about you guys but that
sounds very familiar to me because see
when I read my Bible it tells me that
the Fallen man is like a brute
Beast the Fallen man has an animal
nature but guess what when God comes
into your life
something begins to happen a
change begins to
occur and and and we used to at one time
in the as the old man we used to act
like
animals we used to act like like beasts
what Drew calls brute beast but when the
when the gospel of Christ comes into
your life beloved something begins to
happen a
transformation begins to
occur and by the grace of
God this year you are
better than you were last
year you see Beloved the Plan of
Salvation comes to us and it says I'm
going to make you a new creation a new
creature in Christ and when we become
that new creature in Christ something
begins to happen let me explain it this
way if I can you see according to 2
Corinthians 3:18 the Bible says that by
beholding we become
changed that's
transformation we we we are changed but
we're really changed in two ways let me
share with you the process of
Salvation number one uh um there is a
process of
justification anyone know what
justification is
when God determines you to
be righteous amen now when when is one
Justified right at the moment they
accept Jesus okay is that a process or
is it
instant it's
instant David wrote create in me a clean
heart and renew a right spirit in me the
pro process of justification is instant
it's like God's creative power listen
today I declare you a new man a new
woman amen you are you are Justified
instantly there's no waiting for
justification there's no waiting for the
promise when you say Lord I let you into
my heart in that instant God recreates
You In His Image he purifies you
cleanses you from all your sins amen now
that's the process of justification it
is instant in a moment now what comes
after
justification sanctification I got a
question for you is sanctification
instant
no it's what it's the process of a
lifetime so check this out over a
lifetime you are
evolving over a lifetime you you are the
word evolve simply means changing yeah
you are changing listen the way I was 10
years ago when I accepted Christ should
be uh the the way I am today should be
different from the way I was 10 years
ago when I accepted Christ yeah in other
words the Christian is constantly
getting
better over
time now you're wondering man that
sounds there's a counterfeit to that and
it is true the counterfeit is in what
evolution teaches that man gets
naturally better over
time no beloved that's a counterfeit
it's a counterfeit of a spiritual
reality that when Christ comes into our
life he justifies us immediately
creative power of the word of God Amen
but then we have to learn we have to
learn how to walk we have to learn how
to grow in Grace and so we are
transformed we are being we are are are
evolving getting better over time so
five years ago I used to curse now I
don't I'm not not me not me not me not
me just say you're okay you get the
point I'm trying to make you know and
last year I was doing this this year
look I've grown a
little I I I've changed a little so so
the the the evidence of transitional
forms of life is really in the spiritual
walk okay the evidence you know they
talk about the missing link yeah
listen the
evidence the
evidence of God's power of
evolution is in your changed
life so you know how they do pictures of
the fossils and you know look just
imagine them taking pictures of you like
exhibit a this is you you know in
2006 exhibit B look this is you in 2007
you look a little different right this
is you in 2008 look you're doing things
different you see God desires us beloved
to evolve as a
witness God desires us to evolve as a
witness what does that mean first of all
in our action and secondly in our
activity so in our action what does that
mean it means that now that before I was
you know my witness wasn't really that
good you know I would I would slip up
and you know say this inappropriate
thing or you know and I was trying but
man I'm just because I'm I'm evolving
because I'm transitioning man it's hard
but it's a wrestle it's a daily struggle
sanctification is a daily struggle but
lo and behold over long periods of time
because you are trusting that when the
word of God says that I'm going to H H
uh cleanse you from your sins I'm going
to make you into a better individual you
trust that word and over long periods of
time you find look at this last year I
was doing this last month I was doing
this but man I am getting better and not
me but Christ in me is making me a
better
person yeah so so as a witness you are
growing in your witness so other people
look around say man I remember that you
know when I would look at you I would
you know see this and you would do this
and now as I've been watching you man
you have been
growing that's that's God's God's
evolutionary
power he is evolving us into His Image
we are moving from the image of
animals to the image of Christ the son
of God the man of God yeah so God is
making these transitions moving us from
Beast to
man yeah
so when God does this work within us it
is a work that reveals the power of God
to change us his
evolutionary power his sanctifying power
by the way not only are are we to be
better Witnesses in our actions but
better Witnesses in our
activity you see when I just came into
the church yeah you know what I I I
think I told you guys this before I was
fearful to get up in front of people and
speak and guess what
today I am still fearful to get up in
front of people in scho so let's not use
that example use something else uh the
fact is I do
it you know before it was like I'm not
doing it now I do it even though it's
still like man when I get up and speak
you know I'm going to say something
stupid you all kinds of crazy thoughts
coming into your mind will I mess up
look someone down there is laughing
what's going
on all kinds of crazy
thoughts but the fact is When God says I
call you to be a
witness what you may not have wanted to
do two years ago you should be willing
to do
now God we are to be advancing evolving
in our work as Witnesses so I've never
given a Bible study well God says you're
not
evolving I I need you to be evolving I
need you to be growing better over time
oh I give Bible studies but they're
horrible well don't worry keep giving
them and you'll get
better keep preaching and you'll get
better keep teaching and you'll get
better so beloved if we are denying The
evolutionary power of God we are denying
his power to make us better beings in
Christ genuine
evolution is
this Evolution out in the world is a
counterfeit not of creation it is a
counterfeit of the work of Salvation
that God does in the human
soul
so the Bible tells us let this hope or
this is our hope that Christ be formed
within us this is the hope of glory this
is the transition that is to be taking
place within us and as we learn how to
trust in the word of God as we learn how
to have evidence how to how to hold on
to that evidence we are changed into his
image and our faith is
strengthened one last point we talked
about
adaptation the evolutionist believes
that only those who adapt survive
only those who adapt to their
environment
survive only those that adapt to their
survive you see beloved
listen there are two environments in
this
world there is the
environment of this
world and then the there is the
environment of heavenly
places the Bible tells tell us that God
Has Lifted us up
into Heavenly places which means that
and he's done it now when we believe in
him by faith he raises us up into
Heavenly places now which means that if
I want to survive the second
coming I must
adapt to the atmosphere of
Heaven if I do not adopt
I will not
survive so the devil is busy trying to
get us to adapt to this environment why
because he knows that this environment
is going to be destroyed one
day and so for those who adapt to this
world will be destroyed when the
environment is
destroyed so Jesus says listen I want
you to adapt to the Everlasting
environment when you are fit when you
are able to adapt to the Everlasting Las
in environment when I come again you'll
survive it will truly be survival of the
fittest so Jesus says he who puts his
hand to the plow and looks back is not
fit is not what fit for the Kingdom of
Heaven what does that mean it means if
you start the work of God and then look
back go
backward devolve instead of
evolve if you go backward you will find
yourself unfit for my
kingdom beloved let me sum it up to
you
evolution is a
counterfeit but it is not a counterfeit
of what we
think it is a counterfeit of the genuine
process of
Salvation God looks looks at you and he
says listen I can bring order out of
your chaotic
life I can bring order out of your
catalog you see Satan uses Evolution to
try to disprove God when true Evolution
proves
God because you are the greatest
evidence for
God when you you you say you want to see
Evolution let me show you my life let me
show you what God has done in me and
through me let me show you the power of
God's word you see Beloved the Bible
speaks of something called prophecy
anyone ever heard of Prophecy you know
what prophecy
is like prophecy is Faith on
steroids yeah prophecy is God saying
thousands of years in advance listen oh
by the way AB B CDE e f and
g and not hundreds of years not 20 years
30 years but thousands of
years that's why beloved when a
prophetic event is fulfilled hundreds
and thousands get converted like in an
instant why because they're like look at
this the the word of God is true we can
trust in it beloved that's why as the
Adventist Church we teach prophecy so
much because prophecy is a demonstration
of faith in God's
word why we can have faith in God's word
because look thousands of years ago he
said that this was going to happen in 7
1998 this was going to happen in 1844
and look it happened so if it happened
you and I can rest assured that the
promises of God are like
prophecies the promises of God are like
prophecies so beloved when you're
reading the book of Psalms and you're
you're reading all these Pro
promises remember this this promise is
really a prophecy because though it's
not coming to pass now be coming to pass
now in my life God's word will
prosper in the thing where to he sent it
it will come to pass because his
promises are sure and as you live on
that faith in God's word your faith is
strengthened and there is no way that
Satan can sift
you because you are now standing solidly
on the word of God
and so beloved my simple
appeal is
this God desires
us to be a better
witness both in our actions that is our
lives and in our activities that is our
sharing of our faith if you are not
evolving you are
devolving there is no standing still
you either getting better over time or
you are getting worse over
time beloved I believe that God desires
us to get better over time I believe
that God desires us to be fully
recreated in His image from man from
Beast to man from
chaos to
order God wants to make us New
Creations so if it is your desire to say
Lord I want to experience your
evolutionary power in my
life I want to be better this time next
year no this time next
week some of us need it like next
week we don't have a year you need a
week you Lord begin the process in me
help me to have faith that your word
will do what it says it will do is that
is that your prayer I just want to raise
your hand as your prayer Lord Heavenly
Father we thank you for speaking to
us we thank you for revealing to us that
you desire us to be
changed you desire us to
evolve from worse to better father
remind us we know that justification is
is in an instant but sanctification is
the process of a
lifetime where you you make us better
than we were you move us from the image
of beasts to the image of Christ the son
of
God fix us Lord May Our Lives be
evidence of your evolutionary
power father thank you for revealing to
us that evolution is really a creation
of the the genuine process of faith and
salvation and all the more why it should
be rejected because it takes that which
is true in the spiritual realm and
applies it to the literal realm in an
effort to deny your very
existence Lord we thank you for the work
that you desire to do within us cleanse
us forgive us justify us in an instant
and then Lord be with us throughout our
lifetime that we may ever be increasing
in your grace in your knowledge and in
your goodness we pray this in Jesus name
amen